Police Closing in on Hyakko Party
What did you just say?
If you're unable to understand,
I'll say it as many times as you please.
Your group has acted too often and too recklessly.
It's only a matter of time before the police learn everything they might wish to know about you.
Therefore, Lord Kershner will no longer supply you with—
So you're leaving us out to dry after everything we've done for you.
Is this how you people do things?
You accepted our aid even as you called for the expulsion of all foreigners. You have no right to—
Don't twist things around.
I have no memory of us receiving aid from any barbarians!
We've just been playing along with the whims of some monsters.
Looks like we've got something to take care of before our Showa Restoration!
We're going monster hunting!
If I'm to live
by inertia
There's probably nothing
wrong with giving up
But I don't want the night stolen from me
The moon shines down on me as if to comfort my shuttered heart
I'm left with only a cold blade
I'm just losing myself
I'm searching
Just like this planet that's lost everything
I don't think that I'm always right
But I'm not going to regret what I do now
Making just one wish, I fade into the night
Heav—
Good work.
Come on, pull your weight here!
I am. I'm the brains.
This is strange.
Huh?
It's the Hyakko Party. They haven't been assaulting any scholars or doctors lately.
In fact, not once since Doctor Hanada was attacked by vampires.
Which means that they've finished gathering what they wanted.
Philip, grab those investigation reports we borrowed yesterday.
What? I've had enough of—
I'll go get them.
Hyakko Party Investigation
Yuliy's unusually participative.
It's probably just 'cause he's feeling better.
Well, whatever the reason, I'm glad.
Excuse me.
Hello there, Miss Ryouko.
My father is asking if you'd all like to join us for dinner tonight.
That sounds kind of formal.
And kids don't understand etiquette, after all.
Huh? Yeah I do!
I'll show you my perfect table manners!
We and the Professor will gladly take you up on that.
Thank you! I'll tell my father that...
Miss Ryouko? What's up?
Nothing!
I'll be looking forward to tonight.
Is this what you needed?
Huh? Yeah, thanks.
Is there anything else you need?
This should be all for now.
Okay, then.
Did you see that?
Oh, you bet I did.
Huh? What'd you see?
I never expected to receive a visitor from our rivals at V Shipping!
Come now, I wouldn't call us rivals. Our firms are both engaged in business far from home.
We ought to cooperate with each other.
But of course.
However, I believe that the goods we're dealing with right now are outside your specialty.
The importation of weapons and military tech, correct?
Alma Company always acts while looking ten to twenty years ahead.
Perhaps because of that, upper management has been forming a strong connection with the military here.
I must say I'm quite envious.
No no, your firm has been achieving some—
Excuse me!
Nice, I made it.
Oh? You're...
Sorry for stopping you out of the blue as you left your home the other day.
This is quite the coincidence.
Here to scout out your enemy's stronghold? How diligent.
So, what did you think of Alma Company?
We merely spoke on the future of the shipping industry.
Oh, stop kidding around.
Oh, by the way, I heard about the disappearance of Doctor Hanada.
Were you all alright?
I'd heard that one of your employees got caught up in the incident.
Thank you for your concern.
You know a lot for a reporter, I must say.
That's how I make my living, after all.
Even without hunting for them,
all kinds of rumors find their way to me.
For instance...
Ones that claim that Doctor Hanada didn't disappear, but was in fact killed.
When we met, it was the Doctor's residence you were in such a hurry to get to, wasn't it?
You should do your cover job more convincingly, Mister Willard.
I could say the same.
Alma Company and V Shipping...
The latter certainly acts more suspicious, but...
When I saw someone who was supposed to be in Harbin wandering around Ginza in plainclothes,
I couldn't help but call to them.
It's an honor.
There must be something quite serious happening, if they called you back.
Yes, sir. I'm being worked to the bone.
Oh yes, congratulations on your promotion to the head of the weaponry department.
Major General Kakizaki.
Word always seems to reach you quickly.
I was just in Ichigayadai giving some words of
encouragement to the man replacing me as superintendent.
I consider myself very fortunate to have been enrolled while you were teaching, sir.
Are you on your way to give encouragement to someone else?
No, I'm heading to an inspection in Gotemba.
You're going to an inspection in person?
Will they be demonstrating a new weapon as part of their exercises or something?
It's a military secret, so I can't say more.
Forgive me.
Of course.
But I'll tell you this, Iba.
That thing may well be able to change the nature of war.
It would have most likely been impossible for Japan to develop without assistance.
Is Alma Company that "assistance"?
It seems that steering you into intelligence was a excellent idea.
Another great war will one day occur.
If we can put that weapon to use, there will be no need
to send our men to their death as we have before.
I must ensure that this upcoming exercise is a success.
This morning, officers charged into the Hyakko Party's hideout,
but it seems it was already abandoned.
Anything left behind?
No.
But they do say that there were traces of a fight and something like ash near the building.
So they were teamed up with the vampires.
But then why have they started fighting each other?
After the Hyakko Party gathered the materials they needed, I suppose they had no more use for them.
The question is, what did they do with it all?
Might Alma Company be involved?
That's where all the equipment they stole is?
How was it?
It's an ambitious but upstanding firm.
They're marketing a new weapon to the military right now,
and were even so kind as to tell me that there would be a demonstration in Shizuoka.
Do you think that those "upstanding" employees know that their new weapon may well be stained in blood?
Most likely not.
But we know the shadow behind it all.
And they might be at the exercise as well.
This might be a chance to hunt some royals.
Sounds fun!
So what will we do about the Hyakko Party?
I don't think they'll view the vampires' betrayal as water under the bridge.
Shall we split into two groups?
Professor.
Mochizuki!
Get me a ticket to Gotemba, quick!
Gotemba?
You're going to leave the capital?
I need to monitor Alma Company's activities there.
Alma?
What are we doing about V Shipping then?
It wouldn't be fair for us to only harass them, would it?
V Shipping and Alma Company.
What kind of mischief are they cooking up in this country?
What perfect table manners, young master.
First of all, I can't use chopsticks.
And second, can I point out that this is raw!
Is Japanese cooking not to your liking, perhaps?
Of course it is!
We're happy to be able to dine on the only cuisine with fish this fresh.
We're also overjoyed at the opportunity to have so many guests for dinner.
My wife suffered an early death,
so it's normally just me and my daughter.
This is unusual, Ryouko. Usually you'd be on your second bowl of rice by now.
Father!
Sorry, sorry.
By the way, Professor, how goes your work?
You seem quite busy.
All thanks to the privilege of using your house as a base of operations.
I suppose I should mention that some of our employees will be going on a business trip tomorrow.
Oh?
Where to?
Gotemba, in Shizuoka.
There's a highly valued customer of ours there.
Um... Who will you be sending?
That would be me.
What is it, Ryouko?
It's nothing...
Don't you worry, Miss Ryouko.
I'll be going along to babysit him.
That's right! You don't have to worry about Yuliy.
Look, he's not even fazed.
Um, lets get back to dinner!
What a strange girl you are.
You'd be best off not getting any closer to me.
H-He's...
This is...
Major General Kakizaki.
Has our new product grabbed your attention?
Alma Company looks forward to a fruitful business relationship.
The Ark of Sirius?
You still parrot such nonsense in—
It is not nonsense.
It is what will become the foundation of our prosperity.
Do you think you can lay that "foundation" with the treasure of those filthy wolves?
Would you rather have me sit back and watch as our race dies out?
If that is fate, then there is nothing to be done about it.
Hold, Yevgraf.
This is insolence.
I've nothing more to say to you.
Lord Yev!
Lord Yev! Lord Yev!
Guess what we heard!
That is good news.
You geezers, who have lost your pride as vampires...
If you aim to die out,
do not drag the rest of us into it.
This might not have been the best idea.
What?
Don't worry about it.
I'm finding that difficult.
Then I'll ask. Why did you ask to be on the Gotemba team, Yuliy?
No real reason. It just seemed like I'd be able to kill a lot of vampires.
There's no need to rush—
I can't just wait...
I can't just sit idle.
And also...
Also?
It's nothing.
Also,
if I go, I might be able to meet my brother.
Don't you think you'd get more business if you served alcohol during the day?
If I get too much business, it will become difficult to do my other job.
I'm quite thrilled, you know.
I can finally contribute to the organization.
Don't get too eager.
Our enemy are nothing like human villains.
I'm glad to hear that.
Yes, so was I.
Who do you people thi—
Punishment!
There are two different types of vampire.
The nobles, or Royals,
and the Slaves who serve them.
That's how we call them.
Slaves disguise themselves as humans and protect their eyes with specially-made lenses.
If they didn't, they'd be turned into ashes by the sun's light.
And the Royals?
They're strong even without revealing their true monstrous form,
and they can move unimpeded by the sunlight.
They can blend in with humans with no difficulty.
That's unpleasant to think about.
So, has your investigation borne fruit?
Yes. It seems that not only have the Hyakko Party lost all of their hideouts in the capital,
but they have also stopped getting funds from their sponsor as well.
And that sponsor was?
Just as you'd anticipated.
Alma Company.
I'm borrowing your phone.
Well, that's not right.
Hey boss!
None of them are turning to ash!
Maybe they're not really dead yet?
So we weren't the only humans the monsters paid to work for them.
Where's Kershner?
I don't know!
Where is—
The president's gone to Gotemba for a test of a new weapon!
New weapon?
Tell me everything you know!
It looks like we'll be stopping for a bit while they set up the train to cross the mountain.
I see.
"Oh! I didn't think we'd all be on the same train together!"
"I'm on my way to Hakone..."
That won't work.
Wow, that looks tasty!
Don't eat in such a rush.
Look, you've got it all over your face.
"I just bought some lunch.
Would you like to eat it with me?"
Perfect!
Put me through.
Is that you, Major?
Yes, it's me.
How are things back—
There was a disaster during the exercises in Fuji!
Calm down and tell me what happened.
A whole battalion of infantrymen from Fuji was killed!
What?
We just intercepted a radio message from Gotemba to Headquarters!
"At two zero three zero last night,
an accident occurred during the military
exercises at the foot of Mount Fuji,
and all participating infantrymen have died."
What happened to Major General Kakizaki?
The Major General is fine.
He's already returning to the capital to report on the matter to the Emperor via a special train.
By train?
Major? Major Iba?
What is it, Yuliy?
I smell blood.
Yuliy, wait a minute!
Thank you very much.
Yuliy, wait!
They said it was a massacre.
Professor!
Sorry we're late.
Looks like it's the Hyakko Party.
This is awful.
They're just doing this in broad daylight?
They asked for money and got rejected, I guess.
If they can't get money, then what do they go for next?
Goods, equipment...
Professor?
We need to go to Yuliy and Dorothea!
Did Yuliy forget something in Tokyo?
Excuse me.
Can I see your ticket?
Oh, I'm sorry, I had to change trains.
Could I buy a new one?
Oh yes, in my bag—
Would you like one?
Stop!
Identify yourself!
Military
Handbook
I'm Iba from General Staff HQ.
Military
Handbook
I got on from Kouzu Station in order to carry out my mission.
Military
Handbook
Sir!
Where is Major General Kakizaki?
Here.
Your new ticket.
Thank you.
Now, what reason do you plan to give to the Professor for abandoning our mission?
There are vampires on this train.
I can't track them down any further thanks to the smoke, but they're definitely around.
It wouldn't be ideal to get into a fight here.
I'll go map out where the passengers are.
You stay here.
No, I'll—
You'll stay here.
I don't want you jumping onto another train.
Okay.
Be a good boy.
The experiment ended so fast that I couldn't get enough data.
That result was all the data we need.
Wow!
Personal approval from Lord Kershner!
So once we get back to Tokyo, I can start preparations for mass-production, right?!
I hate depending on a man like that.
Why is Lord Yevgraf so obsessed with an Ark that we don't even know exists?
Rather than clinging to something like that,
I would prefer to take us down a surer path.
Thanks, Mister.
What an unbearable end
I breath out, breath out, breath out, and stop
As I'm fleeing from this cruel world, I fall into a deep sleep
I hide behind the words "I'm doing my best"
But in the end I do nothing but look back
Even when I feel like I've been able to change,
Eventually I realize that the only thing that's changed is the position of the stars
I find myself wondering if everything would feel better if I just broke
Before I fade away while thinking of you,
If I dig out all of my pain then I'll be able to shine like a real star
Will I find a beautiful dream?
This is how we embrace hope
Oh, it's the nuisance from the other day!
Are you not a vampire?
Ten years...
We've had to take quite the detour.
Now, let's start the show!
I'll put you to rest now.